Clement F. Haynsworth Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- United States Court of Appeals File, 1955-1989 (Box 6-201)
  - Case File, 1956-1989 (Box 7-159)
    - 1982 October term
      - United States v. Winstead, No. 82-5251
      - United States v. Cardwell, No. 82-5326
      - Allard v. Short, No. 82-6074
      - Self v. Laws, No. 82-6090
      - Grove v. Hardy, No. 82-6095
      - United States v. Whitley, No. 82-6136
      - United States v. Rogers, No. 82-6208
      - Spruill v. Johnson, No. 82-6323
      - Lewis v. Jackson, No. 82-6367
      - Anderson v. Brown, No. 82-6370
      - Turner v. Schneider, No. 82-6373
      - Abdullah v. Hutto, No. 82-6440
      - Jenkins v. Fleming, No. 82-6468
      - Woods v. Martin, No. 82-6485
      - Day v. McCoy, No. 82-6493
      - Mosley v. Maryland, No. 82-6496
      - Ross v. Reed, No. 82-6537
      - United States v. Bales, No. 82-6555
      - Lykins v. Gondles, No. 82-6565
      - Herring v. Williams, No. 82-6569
      - Cassity v. Garrison, No. 82-6571
      - Dixon v. Townley, No. 82-6573
      - Perry v. Allsbrook, No. 82-6583
      - Staton v. Bumgardner, No. 82-6619
      - Lankford v. Foster, No. 82-6644
      - United States v. Doe, No. 82-6655
      - Nelson v. Garraghty, No. 82-6680
      - Hayes v. Nixon, No. 82-6696
      - Dean v. Kamka, No. 82-6705
      - Smith v. Mitchell, No. 82-6742 (Box 98)
      - Remis v. Large, No. 82-6743
      - Hinkle v. Johnson, No. 82-6783
      - Connor v. St. Paul Fire & Marine Ins. Co., No. 82-6786
      - United States v. Eddleton, No. 82-6798
      - Wheeler v. Loyd, No. 82-6803
      - Dallas v. Boyd, No. 82-6804
      - Settles v. Fleming, No. 82-6810
      - Stevens v. North Carolina Dep't of Corrections, No. 82-6819
      - Ferguson v. Leeke, No. 82-6839
      - Horton v. Martin, No. 82-8039
      - Purvis v. Shields, No. 82-8068
      - Hudgins v. Kelly, No. 82-8098
      - Bright v. Garrison, No. 82-8145
      - Potts v. Woodard, No. 82-8168
      - Stevens v. Hunt, No. 82-8170
      - Watkins v. Laws, No. 82-8171
      - Myers v. Hayes, No. 82-8172
      - Simms v. Garraghty, No. 82-8182
      - Felton v. Stephenson, No. 82-8185
      - Bethea v. Leeke, No. 82-8221
      - Dodson v. Baskerville, No. 82-8231
      - Kenyatta v. Johnson, No. 82-8268
      - In re Hensley, No. 83-1011
      - Chavis v. Ford, No. 83-1032
      - Hunter Douglas, Inc. v. Sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass'n, No. 83-1042
      - Williams v. Marriott Corp., No. 83-1052
      - Bowers v. Commissioner, No. 83-1082
      - DeLoatche v. Heckler, No. 83-1096
      - In re United States, No. 83-1149
      - Public school teacher who reported John W. Hinckley, Jr. v. The Sun writer, Ettlin, No. 83-1175
      - Kruse v. Snowshoe Co., No. 83-1206; (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 99)
      - Sims v. Tellertor, No. 83-1324
      - Jordan v. Federal Energy Regulatory Comm'n, No. 83-1359
      - Ward v. Owens, No. 83-1371
      - Avedisian v. Hubbard, No. 83-1433
      - United States v. Neirman, No. 83-5013
      - United States v. Haynes, No. 83-5016
      - United States v. Eplin, No. 83-5018
      - Lovin v. Proffit, No. 83-6001
      - Bales v. Verdeyen, No. 83-6033
      - Beasley v. Kaestner, No. 83-6040
      - Winfield v. Butler, No. 83-6041
      - Whitehead v. Procunier, No. 83-6043
      - Williams v. Clifton, No. 83-6059
      - Wilbon v. United States Court of Military Appeals, No. 83-6090
      - Clark v. Maryland, No. 83-6123
      - Hairston v. Bass, No. 83-6132
      - Russell v. Baird, No. 83-6154
      - Tydings v. Angelone, No. 83-6244
      - Holsey v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 83-6257
      - Jackson v. Maryland, No. 83-6261
      - United States v. Teasley, No. 83-6266
      - Moore v. Rice, No. 83-6279
      - Robinson v. Stephenson, No. 83-6283
      - Cassidy v. Bass, No. 83-6355
      - Cooper v. Kenney, No. 83-6359
      - Jones v. Garraghty, No. 83-6361 (Box 100)
      - Whorley v. Campbell, No. 83-6384
      - Smith v. Nursing staff, No. 83-6433
      - Ivey v. Stephenson, No. 83-8006
      - Brown v. Rice, No. 83-8007
      - Fulcher v. Stephenson, No. 83-8030
      - Lewis v. Griffin, No. 83-8055
      - Harding v. Garrison, No. 83-8070
      - Reaves v. Stephenson, No. 83-8079
      - Paul v. North Carolina, No. 83-8098
      - Fisher v. Lyles, No. 83-8114
      - Cassity v. Stephenson, No. 83-8136
    - 1983 October term
      - Carter v. Fair, No. 81-1842
      - Adams v. Bethlehem Steel Corp., No. 81-2174
      - United States v. Bland, No. 81-5014
      - United States v. Brewer, No. 81-5306
      - Shah v. Hutto, No. 81-6855; (2 folders)
      - Robinson v. Robinson, No. 82-1107
      - Henson v. Honor Comm. of Univ. of Virginia, No. 82-1110
      - Bradley v. Sadler, No. 82-1285 (Box 101)
      - Egerton v. Marcus, No. 82-1317
      - Miller v. Mercy Hosp., No. 82-1323
      - Couch v. Center Bros., No. 82-1485
      - Gray v. Quality Mechanical Contractors, No. 82-1486
      - Jackson v. Department of the Army, No. 82-1553
      - Hunter v. Schweiker, No. 82-1618
      - Strayer v. Halterman, No. 82-1673
      - Williams v. Virginia Dep't of Educ., No. 82-1734
      - Dostert v. Neely, No. 82-1743
      - Dill v. Secretary of Health and Human Servs., No. 82-1844
      - Associated Dry Goods Corp. v. Equal Employment Opportunity Comm'n, No. 82-1905
      - Mackey v. Nationwide Ins. Cos., No. 82-1912; (2 folders)
      - Tabor v. Schweiker, No. 82-1991
      - Amidon v. Lehman, No. 82-2028
      - Garrett v. Phillips Mills, Inc., No. 82-2037 (Box 102)
      - Tignor v. Parkinson, No. 82-2046
      - Raines v. Schweiker, No. 82-2064
      - Troxler Elecs. Laboratories v. Solitron Devices, No. 82-2078
      - National Posters v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 82-2140
      - Scarborough v. Ridgeway, No. 82-2156
      - Butcher v. Brown, No. 82-2157
      - United States v. Roberts, No. 82-5146
      - United States v. Weatherless, No. 82-5156
      - United States v. Stewart, No. 82-5170
      - United States v. Marra, No. 82-5294
      - United States v. Ordele, No. 82-5342
      - United States v. Gadsden, No. 82-6334
      - Lambert v. Foster, No. 82-6339
      - Barfield v. Harris, No. 82-6424; (2 folders)
      - Milby v. North Carolina Dep't of Corrections, No. 82-6484
      - United States v. Holden, No. 82-6635
      - Richardson v. Sheriff, Johnston County, No. 82-6741
      - United States v. Patterson, No. 82-6744
      - Allgood v. Morris, No. 82-6809
      - Kiriluk v. Baskerville, No. 82-8158
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Modern Mfg. Co., No. 83-1018 (Box 103)
      - Hill v. Watts, No. 83-1078
      - Perkins v. Schweiker, No. 83-1086
      - Six Indus. v. Princeton Towers Assocs., No. 83-1104
      - Thacker v. Schweiker, No. 83-1116
      - Gulf Oil Corp. v. Eggers, Inc., No. 83-1171
      - Gaeta v. Union Home Loan Corp., No. 83-1178
      - Jahangir v. Arlington County Sheriff's Dep't, No. 83-1217
      - Rite-Aid v. Greenville Mall Partners, No. 83-1218
      - Williams v. United States, No. 83-1231
      - Union Boiler Co. v. Secretary of Labor, No. 83-1302
      - Shelton v. Washington Group, No. 83-1319
      - Sarvis v. Seaboard Coastline R.R., No. 83-1346
      - Franklin v. Schweiker, No. 83-1347
      - G. & C. Constr. Corp. v. St. Paul Fire and Marine Ins. Co., No. 83-1348
      - Daniel v. United Mine Workers, No. 83-1410
      - North Carolina Nat'l Bank v. Lawrence Sys., No. 83-1448
      - Oliver v. Aetna Casualty & Sur. Co., No. 83-1466
      - Coastal Inn Assocs. v. City of Virginia Beach, No. 83-1469
      - Scherer v. Napco, Inc., No. 83-1526
      - Cannon v. Allmon, No. 83-1580
      - R. R. Donnelly & Sons Co. v. Belk, No. 83-1602
      - United States v. Phillips, No. 83-1673; (2 folders)
      - Wilson v. Washington Adventist Hosp., No. 83-1688 (Box 104)
      - Keith v. Majestic Mining, No. 83-1696
      - Sessions v. Pabst Brewing Co., No. 83-1703
      - Hilton v. Metcalf, No. 83-1754
      - Benfield v. Chester, No. 83-1755
      - Hensley v. Jenkins, No. 83-1761
      - Byrns v. Chilbar Shipping Co., No. 83-1776
      - Bever v. Gilbertson, No. 83-1790; (2 folders)
      - Sesskin v. Baker, No. 83-1810
      - Armco, Inc. v. Penrod-Stauffer Bldg., No. 83-1874
      - Leviner v. Word, Inc., No. 83-1911
      - Toussaint v. Heckler, No. 83-1912
      - Fuller v. Lee, No. 83-1920
      - Levine v. United States, No. 83-1934
      - Yarn Indus. v. Krupp Int'l, No. 83-1989
      - Evans v. Heckler, No. 83-2025 (Box 105)
      - Bircham v. City of Winston-Salem, No. 83-2032
      - United States v. Currie, No. 83-2038
      - Coffman v. United States, No. 83-2040
      - Stauffer Chem. Co. v. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers, No. 83-2061
      - In re Tyler, No. 83-2141
      - In re Farley, No. 83-2194
      - United States v. Swartout, No. 83-5046
      - United States v. Caron, No. 83-5056
      - United States v. Bodden, No. 83-5073
      - United States v. Gonzalez, No. 83-5076
      - United States v. Wagoner, No. 83-5078
      - United States v. Hinton, No. 83-5095
      - United States v. Hill, No. 83-5124
      - United States v. Daniel, No. 83-5140
      - United States v. Burris, No. 83-5208
      - United States v. Bathgate, No. 83-5211
      - United States v. Kamyan, No. 83-5215
      - United States v. Hathaway, No. 83-5225
      - United States v. Parker, No. 83-5285
      - United States v. McFadden, No. 83-5287
      - Harren v. United States, No. 83-6035
      - Bisping v. Pennington, No. 83-6055
      - Bilal v. Mitchell, No. 83-6060
      - Webb v. Hutto, No. 83-6086
      - Green v. Collins, No. 83-6126 (Box 106)
      - United States v. Collette, No. 83-6165
      - Sutton v. Tinney, No. 83-6176
      - White v. Broughton, No. 83-6183
      - Lockwood v. Mitchell, No. 83-6198
      - Thomas v. Leeke, No. 83-6255
      - Steppe v. Alexandria Circuit Court, No. 83-6269
      - White v. Johnson, No. 83-6367
      - Johnson v. Maryland, No. 83-6368
      - United States v. Chinchello, No. 83-6398
      - Loney v. United States Dep't of Justice, No. 83-6404
      - Anderson v. Procunier, No. 83-6405
      - Remis v. Rogers, No. 83-6420
      - Richardson v. Garrison, No. 83-6431
      - Mabery v. Hinton, No. 83-6491
      - Mabery v. Horton, No. 83-6493
      - Little v. Allsbrook, No. 83-6511
      - Draper v. Guerry, No. 83-6526
      - Austin v. McNamara, No. 83-6534
      - Williams v. Clifton, No. 83-6545
      - Robinson v. Stephenson, No. 83-6548
      - Ikard v. Woodard, No. 83-6577
      - Kimbrough v. Grommes, No. 83-6592
      - Poole v. Pruitt, No. 83-6594
      - Berrier v. Ashley, No. 83-6596
      - United States v. Teasley, No. 83-6602
      - Hensley v. Allsbrook, No. 83-6603
      - Lathan v. Osborne, No. 83-6612
      - Pitzer v. Poling, No. 83-6614
      - Caldwell v. Garraghty, No. 83-6633
      - United States v. Murray, No. 83-6649
      - Wilder v. Bichly, No. 83-6690
      - Drake v. Dale, No. 83-8033
      - Anderson v. Turner, No. 83-8047
      - Epps v. Hutto, No. 83-8080
      - Hair v. Osborne, No. 83-8148
      - Davis v. Allsbrook, No. 83-8154
      - Johnson v. North Carolina, No. 83-8162
      - Rankin v. Garrison, No. 83-8165 (Box 107)
      - Jordan v. Garraghty, No. 83-8192
      - Banks v. Cherry, No. 83-8197
      - Wilkins v. Lyles, No. 83-8212
      - Sellars v. Garrison, No. 83-8273
      - Rohrbaugh v. Office of Workers' Compensation Programs, No. 84-1003
      - Harrell v. United States, No. 84-1011
      - Harris v. Friedline, No. 84-1105
      - Rosenkoff v. Battaglia, No. 84-1124
      - Amrhein v. Subaqueous Exploration & Archaeology, No. 84-1151
      - Carter v. Virginia Dep't of Corrections, No. 84-1334
      - McCann v. Procunier, No. 84-1335
      - In re Jacobs, No. 84-1444
      - Corathers v. Fury, No. 84-1492
      - Weimer v. Internal Revenue Serv., No. 84-1495
      - United States v. Petress, No. 84-6003
      - Doss v. Huggins, No. 84-6020
      - United States v. Jackson, No. 84-6024
      - Novak v. Barksdale, No. 84-6028
      - United States v. Lindsey, No. 84-6047
      - Lykins v. Procunier, No. 84-6062
      - United States v. Hernandez-Perez, No. 84-6065
      - Herring v. Chadwell, No. 84-6114
      - Thompson v. Osborne, No. 84-6136
      - Clark v. Bruce, No. 84-6151
      - Austin v. Woodard, No. 84-6159
      - Hinton v. Garraghty, No. 84-6179
      - Mosley v. Twitty, No. 84-6208
      - Small v. Smith, No. 84-6209
      - Vandiver v. Haunbaker, No. 84-6238
      - Hash v. Camarata, No. 84-6249
      - Myer v. Collins, No. 84-6262
      - Brooks v. Chamblee, No. 84-6272
      - Roudabush v. Vassar, No. 84-6290
      - Turner v. Lyles, No. 84-6292
      - Smith v. Feamster, No. 84-6317
      - Floyd v. Bass, No. 84-6323
      - Bernard v. Sullivan, No. 84-6339(L) (Box 108)
      - Brewer v. Preiser & Wilson Law Firm, No. 84-6415
      - Harrison v. Maryland, No. 84-8023
      - Mills v. Landon, No. 84-8026
      - Small v. Rice, No. 84-8032
      - Jones v. Garraghty, No. 84-8034
      - Bloodgood v. Garraghty, No. 84-8048
      - Brooks v. Rice, No. 84-8078
      - Love v. Stephenson, No. 84-8080
      - Wright v. Landon, No. 84-8092
      - Mitchell v. Maryland, No. 84-8126
      - Clontz v. Whitaker, No. 84-8129
    - 1984 October term
      - United States v. Hunt, No. 81-5211
      - Ferromontan, Inc. v. Georgetown Steel Corp., No. 82-1425
      - Peacock v. Whiteville City Bd. of Educ., No. 82-2110
      - United States v. Snyder, No. 82-5081
      - Colonial Lincoln-Mercury v. Musgrave, No. 83-1057
      - VanGaalen v. Sparks, No. 83-1177
      - Sit-Set, A.G. v. Universal Jet Exch., No. 83-1195
      - Lewis v. Bloomsburg Mills, No. 83-1297
      - Tune v. Sears, Roebuck & Co., No. 83-1355
      - Stearns v. Genrad, Inc., No. 83-1611; (2 folders) (Box 109)
      - Arlosoroff v. National Collegiate Athletic Ass'n, No. 83-1702; (2 folders)
      - Jolles v. Sambat, No. 83-1823
      - Smith v. FCX, No. 83-1993
      - Faulconer v. Commissioner, No. 83-2014
      - United States v. Wise, No. 83-5274
      - Ganey v. Barefoot, No. 83-6281; (2 folders)
      - Summers v. Allsbrook, No. 83-6500
      - Olson v. Leeke, No. 83-6650 (Box 110)
      - Glover v. Cole, No. 84-1033
      - High v. Economics Laboratory, No. 84-1090
      - Klippel v. U-Haul Co., No. 84-1149; (2 folders)
      - Park Corp. v. United States Fidelity & Guar. Co., No. 84-1188
      - McCain Mfg. Corp. v. Rockwell Int'l Corp., No. 84-1301
      - LaRouche v. State Bd. of Elections, No. 84-1324
      - United States v. (Under Seal), No. 84-1329
      - Clark v. E. I. du Pont de Nemours, No. 84-1351
      - Puopulo v. Treadwell, No. 84-1365
      - Redic v. Gary H. Watts Realty Co., No. 84-1393(L)
      - United States v. Combs, No. 84-1431
      - Hull v. Heckler, No. 84-1481
      - Clarkson v. Orkin Exterminating Co., No. 84-1497
      - Nationwide Mut. Ins. Co. v. Cumbee, No. 84-1547
      - Metropolitan Life Ins. Co. v. Thompson, No. 84-1558
      - Myers v. United States, No. 84-1569(L)
      - Parks Chevrolet v. Willis, No. 84-1592 (Box 111)
      - Lindner v. Durham Hosiery Mills, No. 84-1593
      - R. O. Givens Signs v. Town of Nags Head, No. 84-1653
      - Knighton v. Laurens County School Dist. No. 56, No. 84-1655
      - Roberts v. Heckler, No. 84-1665
      - Klein v. Sears, Roebuck & Co., No. 84-1681(L)
      - Hunt v. Phillips, No. 84-1713
      - United Merchants and Mfrs. v. Aiken County Pub. Serv. Auth., No. 84-1752
      - Fourco Glass Co. v. Equibank, No. 84-1780
      - Whitfield v. Jackson, No. 84-1783(L)
      - Byers v. Martin, No. 84-1792
      - Introcaso v. Cunningham, No. 84-1806
      - Hilton v. Glas-Tec, No. 84-1868
      - Sweeney v. Small World Creative Enters., No. 84-1885
      - Shortt v. Director, Office of Workers' Compensation Programs, No. 84-1891
      - Baker v. Harrah, No. 84-1903(L)
      - United States v. Morgan, No. 84-1952(L)
      - United Va. Bank v. Kidd, No. 84-1990
      - Beale v. Whitehead Bros. Co., No. 84-2028
      - Atlantic Nat'l Bank v. Thorpe, No. 84-2149
      - Denton v. Edmisten, No. 84-2225
      - Delmarva Drilling Co. v. Byrd Food, No. 84-2309
      - Chu v. Griffith, No. 84-2318
      - Rout v. Dykes, No. 84-2385 (Box 112)
      - United States v. Price, No. 84-5055
      - United States v. Mallas, No. 84-5085(L)
      - United States v. Green, No. 84-5087
      - United States v. White, No. 84-5091(L)
      - United States v. Smith, No. 84-5102
      - United States v. Paschall, No. 84-5166
      - United States v. Gatewood, No. 84-5211
      - United States v. Smith, No. 84-5240
      - United States v. Brown, No. 84-5247(L)
      - United States v. Kelley, No. 84-5257
      - United States v. Folio, No. 84-5339
      - Farrow v. Moore, No. 84-6084
      - Owens-El v. United States Attorney Gen., No. 84-6241
      - United States v. Hanna, No. 84-6274
      - Brooks v. Plageman, No. 84-6289
      - Arias v. Lowe, No. 84-6303
      - Mathers v. Fisher, No. 84-6313
      - Rosenbaum v. Department of Corrections, No. 84-6329
      - Davis v. Buckingham Correctional Center, No. 84-6347(L)
      - United States v. Cimino, No. 84-6350
      - Overton v. Procunier, No. 84-6351
      - Drumheller v. Booker, No. 84-6405
      - Roudabush v. Vassar, No. 84-6407
      - Bowring v. Booker, No. 84-6468
      - United States v. Pella, No. 84-6489
      - Wadhams v. Procunier, No. 84-6501
      - Melton v. Camarata, No. 84-6502 (Box 113)
      - Belsher v. Heckler, No. 85-1005
      - Connor v. PYA/Monarch, No. 85-1055
      - Educational Servs. v. Maryland State Bd. for Higher Educ., No. 85-1060(L)
      - Reichenbach v. Heckler, No. 85-1071
      - Laidman v. Hampton Rds. Marina, No. 85-1161
      - Clinchfield Coal Co. v. District 28, United Mine Workers, No. 85-1171
      - Federal Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Estill and Greenlee, Inc., No. 85-1199
      - Allen v. Commissioner, No. 85-1224
      - Wade v. Heckler, No. 85-1250
      - Southern Bank and Trust Co. v. Rhoades, No. 85-1301
    - 1985 October term
      - Owens v. Schweiker, No. 82-2103
      - Johnson v. Oroweat Foods Co., No. 83-1926(L)
      - United States v. Harvey, No. 83-5256
      - United States v. Johnson, No. 83-5268
      - Garvin v. Alumax of S.C., No. 84-1156; (2 folders)
      - Tims v. Carolina Pools, No. 84-1254; (1 folder) (Box 114)
      - Lohrmann v. Pittsburgh Corning Corp., No. 84-1323
      - Zemonick v. Consolidation Coal Co., No. 84-1353; (3 folders)
      - Clinchfield Coal Co. v. Fuller, No. 84-1530
      - St. Paul Fire & Marine Ins. Co. v. Vaughn, No. 84-1583(L)
      - De Franks v. Mayor, Ocean City, No. 84-1624
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Ensign Elec. Div., No. 84-1658; (2 folders)
      - Triplett v. Brotherhood of Ry., Airline and S.S. Clerks, No. 84-1697
      - M. Kramer Mfg. Co. v. Andrews, No. 84-1710 (Box 115)
      - Wardlaw v. City of Newport News, No. 84-1808
      - Cuthbert v. Secretary, Dep't of Health and Human Servs., No. 84-1841
      - Havee v. Belk, No. 84-1880
      - LaRouche v. Regan, No. 84-1964
      - Burnette v. Nicolet, Inc., No. 84-2063
      - Scott v. Sears, Roebuck & Co., No. 84-2086
      - Cornett v. AVCO Fin. Servs., No. 84-2120
      - Borders v. Heckler, No. 84-2163
      - Maryland State Teachers Ass'n v. Hughes, No. 84-2213
      - Breedlove v. Heckler, No. 84-2263
      - Quillen v. International Playtex, No. 84-2330
      - United States v. Cappleman, No. 84-5016
      - United States v. Sharpe, No. 84-5024
      - United States v. Blackston, No. 84-5089
      - United States v. Uzzell, No. 84-5108
      - United States v. Rhodes, No. 84-5114; (2 folders) (Box 116)
      - United States v. Walsh, No. 84-5194(L)
      - United States v. Brantley, No. 84-5233
      - United States v. Martindale, No. 84-5329
      - United States v. Massaro, No. 84-5330
      - United States v. Church, No. 84-5363
      - McAbee v. Sprinkle, No. 84-6439
      - Strange v. Local Union No. 79, Int'l Ass'n of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, No. 85-1019
      - Taneja v. Smith, No. 85-1035
      - Tri-Continental Leasing Corp. v. Reed, No. 85-1048
      - United States v. (Under Seal), No. 85-1077
      - Francis Denney, Inc. v. New Process Co., No. 85-1131
      - McClelland v. Massinga, No. 85-1138
      - Best View Cablevision v. City of Abbeville, No. 85-1159
      - United States v. United States Fidelity and Guar. Co., No. 85-1209 (Box 117)
      - Stapleton v. Ashland Oil, No. 85-1260
      - Carr v. Riddle, No. 85-1269
      - Krzywicki v. Lash Barge PL-1-0325, No. 85-1273
      - Knowles v. Mutual Life Ins. Co., No. 85-1275
      - Neace v. Heckler, No. 85-1285
      - Boggs v. Sterling Drilling and Prod. Co., No. 85-1294
      - Coleman v. Howell, No. 85-1298
      - Sam Solomon Co. v. Southeast Bank, No. 85-1299
      - Grant v. Manpower Temporary Servs., No. 85-1318
      - Cox v. Lehman, No. 85-1322
      - Fleming v. Moore, No. 85-1361
      - Macaulay v. Life Ins. Co. of N. Am., No. 85-1374; (2 folders)
      - Butler v. Florence County Office of Economic Opportunity Comm., No. 85-1392
      - Noordzee v. United States Fish, No. 85-1408
      - Richardson v. Pitt County, No. 85-1422
      - Ferguson v. Allied Prods. Corp., No. 85-1428
      - Malenki v. Virginia Pet Centers, No. 85-1456
      - Ancona v. Umstadter, No. 85-1470
      - Potts v. Jackson Marine Sales, No. 85-1526
      - R. O. Givens Signs v. Town of Nags Head, No. 85-1540 (Box 118)
      - Johnson v. Town of Elizabethtown, No. 85-1547
      - Gibson v. Caterpillar Tractor Co., No. 85-1552
      - Fierer v. Minchew, No. 85-1569
      - Sine v. Local No. 992, Int'l Bhd. of Teamsters, No. 85-1570
      - Roehling v. National Gypsum Co. Gold Bond Bldg. Prods., No. 85-1571
      - True v. Douglas, No. 85-1632
      - Lilly v. City of Beckley, No. 85-1650
      - McGlone v. Heckler, No. 85-1680
      - Devers v. Chateau Corp., No. 85-1715; (3 folders)
      - Bennett v. Heckler, No. 85-1725
      - Holman v. Patuxent Equip. Co., No. 85-1739
      - Mid-Atlantic Supply v. Three Rivers Aluminum Co., No. 85-1795
      - Freeman v. Sullivan, No. 85-1811
      - Donovan v. Executive Towers, No. 85-1815 (Box 119)
      - Gadell v. Dodson Ins. Group, No. 85-1839
      - Carolina Casualty Ins. Co. v. Insurance Co. of N. Am., No. 85-1909
      - Kiser v. Director, Office of Workers' Compensation Programs, No. 85-1944
      - Askins v. Merry Cos., No. 85-1963
      - Boston v. Heckler, No. 85-1989
      - Harbour v. Hopkins-Lewis Co., No. 85-2010(L)
      - Raby v. Carolina Power and Light, No. 85-2011
      - Ash v. United Parcel Serv., No. 85-2024(L)
      - Dixon v. Westinghouse Elec. Corp., No. 85-2033; (2 folders)
      - Considine v. Reserve Life Ins. Co., No. 85-2036
      - Keval v. Weinberger, No. 85-2069
      - Bordner v. Mutual Assurance Soc'y, No. 85-2114
      - Barnhill v. Firestone Tire & Rubber Co., No. 85-2118
      - Rorrer v. Bullock, No. 85-2153
      - Warren v. Heckler, No. 85-2165
      - Alverson v. Secretary of Health and Human Servs., No. 85-2172
      - Simmons v. Waldman, No. 85-2177
      - Pan Am. Fin. Corp. v. Equifax Servs., No. 85-2188
      - Leake v. Chandler, No. 85-2199
      - Clinchfield Coal Co. v. Department of Interior, No. 85-2206
      - Sisarcick v. Valley Camp Coal Co., No. 85-2218
      - Chrisley v. United States, No. 85-2222
      - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union v. Rob Roy, Inc., No. 85-2234
      - Ardrey v. United Parcel Serv., No. 85-2239
      - Haley v. Blue Ridge Transfer Co., No. 85-2241 (Box 120)
      - Wiggins v. Eastern Associated Coal Corp., No. 85-2246
      - Pinkard v. United States Dep't of Labor, No. 85-2277
      - Armachain v. United States Dep't of Labor Benefits Review Bd., No. 85-2283
      - Virginia Educ. Fund v. Commissioner, No. 85-2296